So we have successfully registered two devices in the server and now we're going to do the last step,
which is: to configure the device.
I'll start with the device called device1-abp.
Then right after, I do the same process with the device called device1-OTAA. Let's start.
My LoRaWAN end-device can be configured from a specific header file.
And the first thing I need to do is to choose the application behavior.
So for this demonstration, I will use ABP activation mode and I will send a temperature every 10 seconds.
That's it.
You don't have to worry about the other settings for the moment.
Now let's copy the LoRaWAN parameters.
So, that address.
Network Station key.
And application session key.
There we go.
Now, I compile the project and I send it to my device.
We can now do the same process with the second device with OTAA activation mode.
My LoRaWAN end device.
Use again the same header file for its configuration.
So, for this demonstration I will use OTAA activation mode and I will send a temperature every 10 seconds.
That's actually the same demonstration that we use for ABP.
Then for the LoRaWAN parameters, I can copy the dev EUI.
The app EUI.
On the Application Key.
I compile the project and send it to my own device.
Now, as soon as I power up my device, then the transmission starts right away.
If it's a OTAA end device, then at the beginning there will be the activation procedure, as
we explained previously.
But whatever the network server  were using
From that point,
We should be able to see the data in the live data section.